Futon, clothes, shoes, toothbrush...
What else?
Huh?!
Rin! Don't disappear on me all of a sudden!
You startled me!
Okay.
Daikichi, get a green one.
Come on! Let's go.
It's dangerous if we don't hold hands.
For me?
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow.
It's different than a sacrifice. Something's off.
I don't think it's like some penalty game.
So, why? I don't get it at all.
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important.
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending.
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy.
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
I want blue!
I don't remember this many families being here before.
I want that!
This?
Yeah.
Umm... All right. Sure, why not?
Any idea what size you are?
I dunno.
Rin, turn around.
Was it like this?
How do I do this..?
I dunno!
Stop flapping your arms!
What else do you need?
Pajamas! Underwear! Shirts! Socks!
You don't need a skirt?
All you've got are pants.
Skirts aren't allowed at the Kindergarten.
I see...
Kindergarten?!
I completely forgot!
Tomorrow's Monday!
Daikichi, I'm tired!
We're almost there, so just hang on.
Okay...
I'm hungry...
We'll be home in a minute, so...
Okay...
You useless bum!
You make everything hard on me!
I'm gonna lose it!
You bastard!
Hey!
Don't touch me!
Let go of me!
Uh, excuse me...
Yes, this is the Maeda residence.
Please accept my condolences for your sudden loss.
Yes, please wait a moment...
Haruko, it's Daikichi.
Uh, okay. Thank you!
Oh, Haruko?
Sorry, I didn't know your cell number.
It's fine.
How do you register for kindergarten?
Kindergarten..?
You really took Rin home?!
Are you sure about this?
For now...
What do you mean, "for now"?
So anyway, I can't take off work tomorrow.
What do I need to do?
Look, they don't accept kids instantly.
Can you do something on your end?
Like what?
Well, I'd check with the city office...
But it's Sunday night.
What?
Sorry, it's just Reina.
Mama, is that Rin?
Is everything okay?
Rin!
Reina, please!
This is important!
Rin!
Well, there's are temporary kindergartens...
A temporary kindergarten...
Rin!
What? Dai?
Rin! Rin! Rin! Rin!
Nevermind.
I'm almost done, so just wait!
I hate waiting!
Haruko, I'm taking the miso soup off the stove.
Okay! Thanks.
Hey... It sounds busy over there, so I'll just call la-
Rin!
Temporary Kindergarten
Man, there aren't that many...
This'll double my commute...
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
This one's pretty close, but I can't get off by six...
Let's play again sometime.
Yeah. Bye-bye, Reina. Talk to you later!
This looks like a good one,
but they'll accept kids for only 10 days...
I want a bath...
Just wait a little longer...
Daikichi! Daikichi!
It's morning...
Yeah... Sorry...
Did you sleep here?
Why is the futon warm?
Take this off!
Yeah, yeah.
So, about the kindergarten we're going to today...
Thank you for the food I'm about to eat!
Thank you for the food...
You're not supposed to eat with your elbow on the table!
There. Sorry.
Listen, the kindergarten you're going to today is only a temporary deal.
Temporary?
Only until we can find you an actual kindergarten.
What's "actual"?
It means "for real"...
Wait, no...
Leave my hair alone!
Are you okay?
I'm fine...
F-Fine...
I see it!
Put me down! Put me down!
What? What?
Would you be embarrassed if other kids saw me carry you or something?
Daikichi...
Yeah...
Well, please take good care of her.
Sure. We'll see you later.
Don't look at me like that!
I won't be able to make it back while it's still light out,
but I'll come as fast as I can.
I promise.
Pinky swear.
If I lie, I swear
I'll swallow 1000 needles...
Damn it!
My finger was cut off!
That's not how the song goes!
Well, see ya! Don't go anywhere.
I'm sorry, Rin.
I didn't consider your feelings.
What happened with your mother or Grandpa wasn't your fault,
but you're still left all alone in this world.
Did you think I was going to leave you behind too?
I'm sorry.
I'll never let that happen to you again...
Read it to me.
Sure.
Kawachi. Wanna get some lunch?
I brought some.
I need to leave a little early today...
Oh, yeah? I'll see you later.
Working really hard from the get-go, huh?
Not exactly.
Take a photo of this sample.
Okay.
Kawachi! You've got a call on line #4 about the private viewing.
Coming.
Hello, this is Kawachi.
Bye-bye!
Let's keep going!
Yeah.
Kawachi...
Yes! Excuse me...
You're late!
Sorry about that. Go and change.
All right!
Rin, don't break it, okay?
Sure...
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye...
Sure, in a second.
Kawachi.
It's Miyata from Mitsutomo Trading.
I'll take it.
Hello, this is Kawachi.
Thank you for your patronage.
Hello, Kawachi here.
Yes...
I'm terribly sorry.
Yes. I'll be able to leave work in a few more minutes, so...
I'm sorry.
The kindergarten is too far!
Rin! Sorry I'm late!
Welcome back!
I'm really... sorry.
Rin...
Are those potatoes?
They look delicious.
It's burdock!
Daikichi
I swallowed
1000 needles!
Please take care of this.
Kawachi! I need your signature!
I probably don't need to worry...
but what'll happen if I get a girlfriend?
Daikichi! Daikichi!
Wake up!
All right... Sorry...
Kawachi, this is what you sent out yesterday, isn't it?
I'm so sorry...
It's unusual for you...
Sorry...
I already apologized to the recipient, so...
Sorry... I give them al call.
We haven't gone out drinking for a while. How about it?
Sorry, tonight's no good.
Then, how about tomorrow?
I've got something tomorrow, too...
Oh, I get it! Good for you, you sly dog.
Here.
I'm fine!
Daikichi!
Hold on tight!
Daikichi! Run away from the moon!
There's no end to this!
How long can I keep this up?
Maternal Health Record
These are Rin's.
This is all she has,
but her maternal handbook and other important documents are in here.
Even if it's only for a short period of time,
raising a child is a very difficult thing.
It's Rin who has it most difficult...
Just gonna take a peek...
She's got the same mouth...
The family talks about you like you're some foul villain.
Is that true?
Masako.
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Why are you sleeping over there now?
M-Me?! Me?!
It's sweat!
Sure, sure... It's sweat.
Sweat...
Help me take the sheet off.
I said it's sweat!
I'm saying it's sweat too, aren't I?!